Or Yaakov

Frontend Developer

Contact Info



🛖 🏻 Maale Adumim, Israel



054-7477745



oryaakov16@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/or-yaakov



https://github.com/oryaakov2

Skills

Java

Spring

Springboot

Hibernate

MySQL

Javascript

Typescript

React

React-Native

Redux

HTML

CSS

OOP

REST API

Github

Familiarity With

Linux

Node.is

xCode

Languages

Hebrew - Native

English - High Level

Summary

I am a 26 years old, Full-Stack Developer with 7 months of programming experience by development significant projects and also small projects.

I have a strong passion for programming, Eager to learn new technologies to expand my knowledge.

I have the ability to finish missions from scratch and excellent team-player.

Experience

Quick-Quiz

Quiz website of random general questions.

- Technologies used in the project: HTML, CSS, Javascript, localstorage.
- Features: Generate random questions, save scores in localstorage, display top 5 scores.

Simon-Says

Mobile game for iOS / Android.

• Technologies used in the project: React-Native, React-Hooks, Typescript, Redux.

Taxi-Station Management

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

Web application for taxi's station to manage the users, rides and driver's monthly reports.

 Technologies used in the project: React, Javascript, React-Hooks, Redux, JSON, HTTP, Firebase, Java, Springboot.

Taxi-App

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

The project includes two mobile applications, one app for customers and second app for drivers.

- Technologies used in the project: React-Native, React-Hooks, Redux, Firebase, Google Maps API, Geolocation.
- Features: A mobile applications that includes real-time locations, rides routing, search origin and destination with autocomplete and display them on the map.

Coupon System

May 2021 - Jul 2021

The business requirement for this project was to deliver a coupon e-commerce system.

- Technologies used in the project: Java, Spring, Springboot, Hibernate, MySQL, React, React-Hooks, Javascript, HTTP, JSON.
- Features: Coupons shopping website includes authentication, purchase coupons, remove outdated coupons automatically. Viewing coupons for purchase and sorting them by date, price, alphabetic.

Education

John Bryce - Graduate with Honors Jun 2020 - Jul 2021:

Java Full Stack Development, GPA 97

Jan 2011 - Jan 2014: **High School Ort Science and Technologies**